<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pink Floyd</string>
    <string name="MCM">In a churchyard by a river\n\nLazing in the haze of midday\n\nLaughing in the grasses and the graves\n\nYellow bird, you are not lone\n\nIn singing and in flying on\n\nIn laughing and in leaving\n\nWillow weeping in the water\n\nWaving to the river daughters\n\nSwaying in the ripples and the reeds\n\nOn a trip to Cirrus Minor\n\nSaw a crater in the sun\n\nA thousand miles of moonlight later\n\nYou got to be crazy</string>
    <string name="MTNS">I was standing by the Nile\n\nWhen I saw the lady smile\n\nI would take her out for a while\n\nFor a while\n\nLike tears left like a child\n\nHow her golden hair was blowing wild\n\nThen she spread her wings to fly\n\nFor to fly\n\nSoaring high above the breezes\n\nGoing always where she pleases\n\nShe will make it to the islands in the sun\n\nI will follow in her shadow\n\nAs I watch her from my window\n\nOne day I will catch her eye\n\nShe is calling from the deep\n\nSummoning my soul to endless sleep\n\nShe is bound to drag me down\n\nDrag me down</string>
    <string name="MCS">We smile and smile\n\nWe smile and smile\n\nLaughter echoes in your eyes\n\nWe climb and climb\n\nWe climb and climb\n\nFootfalls softly in the pines\n\nWe cry and cry\n\nWe cry and cry\n\nSadness passes in a while\n\nWe roll and roll\n\nWe roll and rollv\n\nHelp me roll away the stone</string>
    <string name="MGITC">Heavy hung the canopy of blu  e\n\nShade my eyes and I can see you\n\nWhite is the light that shines through the dress that you wore\n\nShe lay in the shadow of the wave\n\nHazy were the visions of her playing\n\nSunlight on her eyes but moonshine made her blind evry time\n\nGreen is the colour of her kind\n\nQuickness of the eye deceives the mind\n\nEnvy is the bond between the hopeful and the damned</string>
    <string name="MC"> The path you tread is narrow and the drop is sheer and very high\n\nThe ravens all are watching from a vantage point nearby Apprehension creeping like a tube-train up your spine\n\nWill the tightrope reach the end? Will the final couplet rhyme?\n\nAnd its high time, Cymbaline\n\nIts high time, Cymbaline\n\nPlease, wake me\n\nA butterfly with broken wings is falling by your side\n\nThe ravens all are closing in, theres nowhere you can hide\n\nYour manager and agent are both busy on the phone\n\nSelling coloured photographs to magazines back home\n\nAnd its high time, Cymbaline\n\nIts high time, Cymbaline\n\nPlease, wake me\n\nThe lines converging where you stand\n\nThey must have moved the picture plane\n\nThe leaves are heavy around your feet\n\nYou hear the thunder of the train\n\nAnd suddenly it strikes you that theyre moving into range\n\nAnd Doctor Strange is always changing size\n\nAnd its high time! (High time), Cymbaline\n\nIts high time, Cymbaline\n\nPlease, wake me\n\nAnd its high time, Cymbaline\n\nIts high time, Cymbaline\n\nPlease, wake me</string>
    <string name="MIB">Im so afraid\n\nOf all the mistakes that Ive made\n\nShaking every time that I awake\n\nI feel like a cardboard cut-out man\n\nSo build me a time\n\nWhen the characters rhyme\n\nAnd the story line is kind\n\nIve aged and aged since the first page\n\nIve lived every line that you wrote\n\nTake me down, take me down\n\nFrom the shelf above your head\n\nAnd build me a time\n\nWhen the characters rhyme\n\nAnd the story line is kind\n\nI live where Im left\n\nOn the shelf like the rest\n\nAnd the epilogue reads like a sad song\n\nPlease pick up your camera\n\nAnd use me again\n\nAnd build me a time\n\nWhen the characters rhyme\n\nAnd the storyline is kind\n\nYeaaaah\n\n</string>
    <string name="MASP">Pass the tequila, Manuel\n\nListen, gringo, laugh at my lisp and I kill you\n\nI think\n\nThis Spanish music\n\nIt sets my soul on fire\n\nLovely seorita\n\nYour eyes are like stars\n\nYour teeth are like pearls\n\nYour ruby lip\n\n</string>
    <string name="TFCTPWD">Tell me true, tell me why, was Jesus crucified?\n\nWas it for this that Daddy died?\n\nWas it for you? Was it me?\n\nDid I watch too much T.V.?\n\nIs that a hint of accusation in your eyes?\n\nIf it wasnt for the Nips\n\nBeing so good at building ships\n\nThe yards would still be open on the Clyde\n\nAnd it cant be much fun for them\n\nBeneath the rising sun\n\nWith all their kids committing suicide\n\nWhat have we done, Maggie, what have we done?\n\nWhat have we done to England\n\nShould we shout, should we scream\n\nWhat happened to the post war dream?\n\nOh, Maggie, Maggie, what did we do?</string>
    <string name="TFCYPP">They flutter behind you your possible pasts\n\nSome bright-eyed and crazy, some frightened and lost\n\nA warning to anyone still in command\n\nRanks! Fire\n\nOf their possible future, to take care\n\nIn derelict sidings the poppies entwine\n\nWith cattle trucks lying in wait for the next time\n\nDo you remember me? How we used to be?\n\nDo you think we should be closer?\n\n(Closer, closer, closer, closer, closer, closer, closer)\n\nShe stood in the doorway, the ghost of a smile\n\nHaunting her face like a cheap hotel sign\n\nHer cold eyes imploring the men in their Macs\n\nFor the gold in their bags or the knives in their backs\n\nStepping up boldly one put out his hand\n\nHe said, I was just a child then, now Im only a man.\n\nDo you remember me? How we used to be?\n\nDo you think we should be closer?\n\n(Closer, closer, closer, closer, closer)\n\nBy the cold and religious we were taken in hand\n\nShown how to feel good and told to feel bad\n\n(Tongue tied and terrified we learned how to pray\n\nNow our feelings run deep and cold as the clay)\n\nStrung out behind us the banners and flags\n\nOf our possible pasts lie in tatters and rags\n\nDo you remember me? How we used to be?\n\nDo you think we should be closer?\n\n(Closer, closer, closer, closer, closer, closer, closer)</string>
    <string name="TFCOOTF">When youre one of the few to land on your feet\n\nWhat do you do to make ends meet? (Teach)\n\nMake em mad, make em sad, make em add two and two\n\nOr make em me, or make em you, make em do what you want them to\n\nMake em laugh, make em cry, make em lay down and die</string>
    <string name="TFCWTTBF">It was just before dawn one miserable\n\nMorning in black Forty-Four\n\nWhen the forward commander was told to sit tight\n\nWhen he asked that his men be withdrawn\n\nAnd the Generals gave thanks as the other ranks\n\nHeld back the enemy tanks for a while\n\nAnd the Anzio bridgehead was held for the price\n\nOf a few hundred ordinary lives\n\nAnd kind old King George sent Mother a note\n\nWhen he heard that Father was gone\n\nIt was, I recall, in the form of a scroll\n\nWith gold leaf and all\n\nAnd I found it one day\n\nIn a drawer of old photographs, hidden away\n\nAnd my eyes still grow damp to remember\n\nHis Majesty signed with his own rubber stamp\n\nIt was dark all around, there was frost in the ground\n\nWhen the Tigers broke free\n\nAnd no one survived\n\nFrom the Royal Fusiliers Company Z\n\nThey were all left behind\n\nMost of them dead, the rest of them dying\n\nAnd thats how the High Command\n\nTook my daddy from me</string>
    <string name="TFCTHR">Jesus, Jesus, whats it all about?\n\nTrying to clout these little ingrates into shape\n\nWhen I was their age all the lights went out\n\nThere was no time to whine and mope about\n\nAnd even now part of me flies over\n\nDresden at angels one five\n\nThough theyll never fathom it behind my\n\nSarcasm desperate memories lie\n\nSweetheart, sweetheart, are you fast asleep? Good\n\nCause thats the only time that I can really speak to you\n\nAnd there is something that Ive locked away\n\nA memory that is too painful\n\nTo withstand the light of day\n\nWhen we came back from the war\n\nThe banners and flags hung on everyones door\n\nWe danced and we sang in the street and\n\nThe church bells rang\n\nBut the burning in my heart\n\nThe memory smolders on\n\nOf the gunners dying words on the intercom</string>
    <string name="TFCTGD">Floating down, through the clouds\n\nMemories come rushing up to meet me now\n\nBut in the space between the heavens\n\nAnd the corner of some foreign field\n\nI had a dream\n\nI had a dream\n\nGood-bye Max\n\nGood-bye Ma\n\nAfter the service, when youre walking slowly to the car\n\nAnd the silver in her hair shines in the cold November air\n\nYou hear the tolling bell\n\nAnd touch the silk in your lapel\n\nAnd as the tear drops rise to meet the comfort of the band\n\nYou take her frail hand\n\nAnd hold on to the dream!\n\n(Oi!")\n\nA place to stay\n\n("Over here, Morris!)\n\nEnough to eat\n\n(Get back! Get back, John!)\n\nSomewhere old heroes shuffle safely down the street\n\nWhere you can speak out loud\n\nAbout your doubts and fears\n\nAnd whats more, no-one ever disappears\n\nYou never hear their standard issue kicking in your door\n\nYou can relax on both sides of the tracks\n\nAnd maniacs dont blow holes in bandsmen by remote control\n\nAnd everyone has recourse to the law\n\nAnd no one kills the children anymore\n\nNo one kills the children anymore\n\nNight after night\n\nGoing round and round my brain\n\nHis dream is driving me insane\n\nIn the corner of some foreign field\n\nThe gunner sleeps tonight\n\nWhats done is done\n\nWe cannot just write off his final scene\n\nTake heed of the dream\n\nTake heed</string>
    <string name="TFCPE">Button your lip and dont let the shield slip\n\nTake a fresh grip on your bullet proof mask\n\nAnd if they try to break down your disguise with their questions\n\nYou can hide, hide, hide\n\nBehind paranoid eyes\n\nYou put on our brave face and slip over the road for a jar\n\nFixing your grin as you casually lean on the bar\n\nLaughing too loud at the rest of the world\n\nWith the boys in the crowd\n\nYou can hide, hide, hide\n\n(Ill tell you what, Ill give you three blacks, and play you for five")\n\nBehind petrified eyes\n\nYou believed in their stories of fame, fortune and glory\n\nNow youre lost in a haze of alcohol soft middle age\n\nThe pie in the sky turned out to be miles too high\n\nAnd you hide, hide, hide\n\n(Time gentleman!)\n\nBehind brown and mild eyes\n\nOi!</string>
    <string name="TFCGYFHOMD">Brezhnev took Afghanistan\n\nBegin took Beirut\n\nGaltieri took the Union Jack\n\nAnd Maggie, over lunch one day\n\nTook a cruiser with all hands\n\nApparently, to make him give it back</string>
    <string name="TFCTFMH">Take all your overgrown infants away somewhere\n\nAnd build them a home, a little place of their own\n\nThe Fletcher Memorial Home\n\nFor Incurable Tyrants and Kings\n\nAnd they can appear to themselves every day\n\nOn closed circuit T.V\n\nTo make sure they’re still real\n\nIt’s the only connection they feel\n\nLadies and gentlemen, please welcome, Reagan and Haig\n\nMr. Begin and friend, Mrs. Thatcher, and Paisley\n\n“Hello Maggie!”\n\nMr. Brezhnev and party\n\n“Scusi dov’è il bar?”\n\nThe ghost of McCarthy,\n\nThe memories of Nixon.\n\n“Who’s the bald chap?”\n\nAnd now, adding colour\n\nA group of anonymous Latin-American meat packing glitterati\n\nDid they expect us to treat them with any respect?\n\nThey can polish their medals and sharpen their smiles,\n\nAnd amuse themselves playing games for awhile\n\nBoom boom, bang bang, lie down you’re dead\n\nSafe in the permanent gaze of a cold glass eye\n\nWith their favourite toys\n\nThey’ll be good girls and boys\n\nIn the Fletcher Memorial Home for colonial\n\nWasters of life and limb\n\nIs everyone in?\n\nAre you having a nice time?\n\n(Goodbye!)\n\nNow the final solution can be applied</string>
    <string name="TFCSD">They disembarked in 45\n\nAnd no-one spoke and no-one smiled\n\nThere were too many spaces in the line\n\nGathered at the cenotaph\n\nAll agreed with the hand on heart\n\nTo sheath the sacrificial Knifes\n\nBut now\n\nShe stands upon Southampton dock\n\nWith her handkerchief\n\nAnd her summer frock clings\n\nTo her wet body in the rain\n\nIn quiet desperation knuckles\n\nWhite upon the slippery reins\n\nShe bravely waves the boys goodbye again\n\nAnd still the dark stain spreads between\n\nTheir shoulder blades\n\nA mute reminder of the poppy fields and graves\n\nAnd when the fight was over\n\nWe spent what they had made, but\n\nIn the bottom of our hearts we felt the final cut</string>
    <string name="TFCTFC">Through the fish-eyed lens of tear stained eyes\n\nI can barely define the shape of this moment in time\n\nAnd far from flying high in clear blue skies\n\nIm spiraling down to the hole in the ground where I hide\n\nIf you negotiate the minefield in the drive\n\nAnd beat the dogs and cheat the cold electronic eyes\n\nAnd if you make it past the shotguns in the hall\n\nDial the combination, open the priesthole\n\nAnd if Im in Ill tell you (Whats behind the wall)\n\nTheres a kid who had a big hallucination\n\nMaking love to girls in magazines\n\nHe wonders if youre sleeping with your new found faith\n\nCould anybody love him\n\nOr is it just a crazy dream?\n\nAnd if I show you my dark side\n\nWill you still hold me tonight?\n\nAnd if I open my heart to you\n\nAnd show you my weak side\n\nWhat would you do?\n\nWould you sell your story to Rolling Stone?\n\nWould you take the children away\n\nAnd leave me alone?\n\nAnd smile in reassurance\n\nAs you whisper down the phone?\n\nWould you send me packing?\n\nOr would you take me home?\n\nThought I oughta bare my naked feelings\n\nThought I oughta tear the curtain down\n\nI held the blade in trembling hands\n\nPrepared to make it but just then the phone rang\n\nI never had the nerve to make the final cut\n\n“Hello? Listen, I think Ive got it."\n\n"Okay, listen, its a- Hahahaha!”</string>
    <string name="TFCNNJ">Fuck all that, weve got to get on with these\n\n(Fuck all that, fuck all that)\n\nGot to compete with the wily Japanese\n\nThere’s too many home fires burning and not enough trees\n\n(Fuck all that)\n\nSo fuck all that, weve gotta get on with these\n\n(Gotta get on with these)\n\nCan’t stop, lose job\n\nMind gone, silicon\n\nTsar bomb, what bomb?\n\nGet away, pay day\n\nMake hay, break down\n\nNeed fix, big six\n\nClick, click\n\nHold on, oh no\n\nBingo! (Bingo!)\n\nMake them laugh, make them cry\n\nMake them dance in the aisles\n\nMake them pay, make them stay\n\nMake them feel okay\n\nNot now John, weve got to get on with the film show\n\n(Gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\nHollywood waits at the end of the rainbow\n\n(End of the rainbow)\n\nWho cares what it’s about as long as the kids go\n\n(As long as the kids go)\n\nSo, not now John, weve gotta get on with the show\n\n(Gotta get on with the show, gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\n(Gotta get on, gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\nHang on John Ive got to get on with this\n\n(Gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\nI don’t know what it is, but it fits on here like- tsss\n\nCome at the end of the shift, we’ll go and get pissed\n\nBut not now John, Ive gotta get on with this\n\n(Gotta get on with this, gotta get on)\n\nHold on John, I think there’s something good on\n\nI used to read books but...\n\nIt could be the news, or some other amusement\n\nCould be reusable shows\n\nFuck all that, weve gotta get on with these\n\n(Doo, doo, wah)\n\nGot to compete with the wily Japanese\n\n(Gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\nNo need to worry about the Vietnapeace\n\n(Doo, doo, wah)\n\nGot to bring the Russian Bear to his knees\n\n(Gotta get on)\n\nWell, maybe not the Russian Bear, maybe the Swedes\n\n(Doo, doo, wah)\n\nWe showed Argentina, now let’s go and show these\n\n(Gotta get on, gotta get on)\n\nMake us feel tough and wouldnt Maggie be pleased?\n\n(Doo, doo, wah)\n\nNa, na, na, na, na, na, na\n\nOne, two, Free Four!\n\n(One, two, Free Four!)\n\nScusi, dovè il bar? (What?)\n\nSe parakalo, pou einai to bar?\n\nS’il vous plaît, où est le bar? (Say it in English, fairy!)\n\nOi, where’s the fucking bar John? (Oh, now you’re talking!)\n\n(Rule Britannia! Britannia rules the day)\n\nDown! Go, Maggie!\n\nHammer, Hammer, Hammer, Hammer, now!</string>
    <string name="TFCTSITS">In my rear view mirror the sun is going down\n\nSinking behind bridges in the road\n\nAnd I think of all the good things\n\nThat we have left undone\n\nAnd I suffer premonitions, confirm suspicions\n\nOf the holocaust to come\n\nThe rusty wire that holds the cork that keeps the anger in\n\nGives way and suddenly it’s day again\n\nThe sun is in the east\n\nEven though the day is done\n\nTwo suns in the sunset, hmph\n\nCould be the human race is run\n\nLike the moment when the brakes lock\n\nAnd you slide towards the big truck (“Oh no!”)\n\nYou stretch the frozen moments with your fear (*Scream*)\n\nAnd you’ll never hear their voices ("Daddy, Daddy!")\n\nAnd you’ll never see their faces\n\nYou have no recourse to the law anymore\n\nAnd as the windshield melts and my tears evaporate\n\nLeaving only charcoal to defend\n\nFinally I understand\n\nThe feelings of the few\n\nAshes and diamonds, foe and friend\n\nWe were all equal in the end\n\n“…and now the weather. Tomorrow will be cloudy with scattered showers spreading from the east …\n\nWith an expected high of 4000 degrees Celsius”</string>
    <string name="APOTW1">If you didnt care\n\nWhat happened to me\n\nAnd I didnt care\n\nAbout you\n\nWe would zigzag our way through the boredom and pain\n\nOccasionally glancing up through the rain\n\nWondering which of the buggers to blame\n\nAnd watching\n\nFor pigs on the wing</string>
    <string name="AD">You got to be crazy\n\nYou gotta have a real need\n\nYou gotta sleep on your toes\n\nAnd when youre on the street\n\nYou got to be able to pick out the easy meat\n\nWith your eyes closed\n\nAnd then moving in silently\n\nDown wind and out of sight\n\nYou got to strike when the moment is right\n\nWithout thinking\n\nAnd after a while\n\nYou can work on points for style\n\nLike the club tie\n\nAnd the firm handshake\n\nA certain look in the eye and an easy smile\n\nYou have to be trusted\n\nBy the people that you lie to\n\nSo that when they turn their backs on you\n\nYoull get the chance to put the knife in\n\nYou gotta keep one eye\n\nLooking over your shoulder\n\nYou know, its going to get harder\n\nAnd harder and harder\n\nAs you get older\n\nYeah, and in the end, youll pack up\n\nAnd fly down south\n\nHide your head in the sand\n\nJust another sad old man\n\nAll alone and dying of cancer\n\nAnd when you lose control\n\nYoull reap the harvest you have sown\n\nAnd as the fear grows\n\nThe bad blood slows and turns to stone\n\nAnd its too late to lose the weight\n\nYou used to need to throw around\n\nSo have a good drown, as you go down all alone\n\nDragged down by the stone\n\nStone, stone, stone, stone\n\nGot to admit\n\nThat Im a little bit confused\n\nSometimes it seems to me\n\nAs if Im just being used\n\nGotta stay awake, gotta try and shake off\n\nThis creeping malaise\n\nIf I dont stand my own ground\n\nHow can I find my way out of this maze?\n\nDeaf, dumb and blind You just keep on pretending\n\nThat everyones expendable\n\nAnd no one has a real friend\n\nAnd it seems to you, the thing to do\n\nWould be to isolate the winner\n\nEverythings done under the Sun\n\nBut you believe at heart everyones a killer\n\nWho was born in a house full of pain?\n\nWho was trained not to spit in the fan?\n\nWho was told what to do by the man?\n\nWho was broken by trained personnel?\n\nWho was fitted with collar and chain?\n\nWho was given a pat on the back?\n\nWho was breaking away from the pack?\n\nWho was only a stranger at home?\n\nWho was ground down in the end?\n\nWho was found dead on the phone?\n\nWho was dragged down by the stone?\n\nWho was dragged down by the stone?</string>
    <string name="AP">Big man, pig man\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nWooh!\n\nYou well-heeled big wheel\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nAnd when your hand is on your heart\n\nYoure nearly a good laugh, almost a joker\n\nWith your head down in the pig bin\n\nSayin, "Keep on digging"\n\nPig stain on your fat chin\n\nWhat do you hope to find\n\nDown in the pig mine?\n\nYoure nearly a laugh\n\nYoure nearly a laugh, but youre really a cry\n\nBus stop rat bag\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nYou fucked up old hag\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nYou radiate cold shafts of broken glass\n\nYoure nearly a good laugh\n\nAlmost worth a quick grin\n\nYou like the feel of steel\n\nYoure hot stuff with a hatpin\n\nAnd good fun with a handgun\n\nYoure nearly a laugh\n\nYoure nearly a laugh, but youre really a cry\n\nHey you, Whitehouse\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nYou house proud town mouse\n\nHaha, charade you are\n\nYoure tryin to keep our feelings off the street\n\nYoure nearly a real treat\n\nAll tight lips and cold feet\n\nAnd do you feel abused?\n\nGotta stem the evil tide\n\nAnd keep it all on the inside\n\nMary, youre nearly a treat\n\nMary, youre nearly a treat, but youre really a cry</string>
    <string name="AS">Harmlessly passing your time in the grassland away\n\nOnly dimly aware of a certain unease in the air\n\nYou better watch out\n\nThere may be dogs about\n\nIve looked over Jordan, and I have seen\n\nThings are not what they seem\n\nWhat do you get for pretending the dangers not real\n\nMeek and obedient, you follow the leader\n\nDown well trodden corridors into the valley of steel\n\nWhat a surprise!\n\nA look of terminal shock in your eyes\n\nNow things are really what they seem\n\nNo, this is no bad dream\n\nThe Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want\n\nHe makes me down to lie\n\nThrough pastures green He leadeth me the silent waters by\n\nWith bright knives He releaseth my soul\n\nHe maketh me to hang on hooks in high places\n\nHe converteth me to lamb cutlets\n\nFor lo, He hath great power, and great hunger\n\nWhen cometh the day we lowly ones\n\nThrough quiet reflection, and great dedication\n\nMaster the art of karate\n\nLo, we shall rise up\n\nAnd then well make the buggers eyes water\n\nBleating and babbling we fell on his neck with a scream\n\nWave upon wave of demented avengers\n\nMarch cheerfully out of obscurity into the dream\n\nHave you heard the news?\n\nThe dogs are dead!\n\nYou better stay home\n\nAnd do as youre told\n\nGet out of the road if you want to grow old</string>
    <string name="APOTW2">You know that I care\n\nAnd I know that you care for me too\n\nSo I dont feel alone or the weight of the stone\n\nNow that Ive found somewhere safe to bury my bones\n\nAnd any fool knows a dog needs a home\n\nA shelter from pigs on the wing</string>
    <string name="WYWHSOYCD1">Remember when you were young, you shone like the sun\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nNow thers a look in your eyes, like black holes in the sky\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nYou were caught on the crossfire of childhood and stardom\n\nBlown on the steel breeze\n\nCome on you target for faraway laughter\n\nCome on you stranger, you legend, you martyr, and shine\n\nYou reached for the secret too soon, you cried for the moon\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nThreatened by shadows at night, and exposed in the light\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nWell you wore out your welcome with random precision\n\nRode on the steel breeze\n\nCome on you raver, you seer of visions\n\nCome on you painter, you piper, you prisoner, and shine</string>
    <string name="WYWHWTTM">Welcome, my son\n\nWelcome to the machine\n\nWhere have you been?\n\nIts alright, we know where youve been\n\nYouve been in the pipeline, filling in time\n\nProvided with toys and Scouting for Boys\n\nYou bought a guitar to punish your ma\n\nYou didnt like school\n\nAnd you know youre nobodys fool\n\nSo welcome to the machine\n\nWelcome, my son\n\nWelcome to the machine\n\nWhat did you dream?\n\nIts alright, we told you what to dream\n\nYou dreamed of a big star\n\nHe played a mean guitar\n\nHe always ate in the Steak Bar\n\nHe loved to drive in his Jaguar\n\nSo welcome to the machine</string>
    <string name="WYWHHAC">Come in here, dear boy, have a cigar, yore gonna go far\n\nYore gonna fly high, yore never gonna die\n\nYore gonna make it if you try, there gonna love you\n\nWell, ve always had a deep respect a I mean that most sincerely\n\nThe band is just fantastic, that is really what I think\n\nOh, by the way, which ons Pink?\n\nAnd did we tell you the name of the game, boy?\n\nWe call it riding the gravy train\n\nWre just knocked out, we heard about the sell-out\n\nYou gotta get an album out, you owe it to the people\n\nWre so happy we can hardly count\n\nEverybody else is just green, have you seen the chart?\n\nIs a hell of a start, it could be made into a monster\n\nIf we all pull together as a team\n\nAnd did we tell you the name of the game, boy?\n\nWe call it riding the gravy train</string>
    <string name="WYWHWYWH">So, so you think you can tell\n\nHeaven from Hell? Blue skies from pain?\n\nCan you tell a green field from a cold steel rail?\n\nA smile from a veil? Do you think you can tell?\n\nDid they get you to trade your heroes for ghosts?\n\nHot ashes for trees? Hot air for a cool breeze?\n\nCold comfort for change? Did you exchange\n\nA walk-on part in the war\n\nFor a lead role in a cage?\n\nHow I wish, how I wish you were here\n\nWere just two lost souls swimming in a fishbowl year after year\n\nRunning over the same old ground, what have we found?\n\nThe same old fears, wish you were here</string>
    <string name="WYWHSOYCD2">Nobody knows where you are\n\nHow near or how far\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nPile on many more layers\n\nAnd Ill be joining you there\n\nShine on you crazy diamond\n\nAnd well bask in the shadow of yesterdays triumph\n\nAnd sail on the steel breeze\n\nCome on, you boy child, you winner and loser\n\nCome on, you miner for truth and delusion, and shine!</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMSTM">Ive been mad for fucking years\n\nAbsolutely years, been over the edge for yonks\n\nBeen working me buns off for bands\n\nIve always been mad, I know Ive been mad\n\nLike the most of us have\n\nVery hard to explain why youre mad\n\nEven if youre not mad</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMBITA">Breathe\n\nBreathe in the air\n\nDont be afraid to care\n\nLeave\n\nBut dont leave me\n\nLook around\n\nChoose your own ground\n\nFor long you live and high you fly\n\nAnd smiles youll give and tears youll cry\n\nAll you touch and all you see\n\nIs all your life will ever be\n\nRun, rabbit, run\n\nDig that hole, forget the sun\n\nAnd when at last the work is done\n\nDont sit down, its time to dig another one\n\nFor long you live and high you fly\n\nBut only if you ride the tide\n\nBalanced on the biggest wave\n\nYou race towards an early grave</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMT">Ticking away the moments that make up a dull day\n\nFritter and waste the hours in an offhand way\n\nKicking around on a piece of ground in your hometown\n\nWaiting for someone or something to show you the way\n\nTired of lying in the sunshine\n\nStaying home to watch the rain\n\nYou are young and life is long\n\nAnd there is time to kill today\n\nAnd then one day you find\n\nTen years have got behind you\n\nNo one told you when to run\n\nYou missed the starting gun\n\nThen you run and you run to catch up with the sun\n\nBut its sinking\n\nRacing around\n\nTo come up behind you again\n\nThe sun is the same in a relative way\n\nBut youre older\n\nShorter of breath\n\nAnd one day closer to death\n\nEvery year is getting shorter\n\nNever seem to find the time\n\nPlans that either come to naught\n\nOr half a page of scribbled lines\n\nHanging on in quiet desperation\n\nIs the English way\n\nThe time is gone\n\nThe song is over\n\nThought Id something more to say\n\nHome\n\nHome again\n\nI like to be here when I can\n\nAnd when I come home cold and tired\n\nIts good to warm my bones beside the fire\n\nFar away across the field\n\nThe tolling of the iron bell\n\nCalls the faithful to their knees\n\nTo hear the softly spoken magic spells</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMTGGITS">I am not frightened of dying\n\nAny time will do, I dont mind\n\nWhy should I be frightened of dying?\n\nTheres no reason for it, youve gotta go sometime\n\nIf you can hear this whispering, you are dying</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMM">Money\n\nGet away\n\nYou get a good job with more pay and youre okay\n\nMoney\n\nIts a gas\n\nGrab that cash with both hands and make a stash\n\nNew car, caviar, four-star daydream\n\nThink Ill buy me a football team\n\nMoney\n\nGet back\n\nIm alright, Jack, keep your hands off of my stack\n\nMoney\n\nIts a hit\n\nDont give me that do-goody-good bullshit\n\nIm in the high-fidelity first class travelling set\n\nAnd I think I need a Lear jet\n\nMoney\n\nIts a crime\n\nShare it fairly, but dont take a slice of my pie\n\nMoney\n\nSo they say\n\nIs the root of all evil today\n\nBut if you ask for a rise, its no surprise\n\nThat theyre giving none away\n\nI was in the right\n\nYes, absolutely in the right\n\nI certainly was in the right\n\nYeah, I was definitely in the right; that geezer was cruising for a bruising\n\nWhy does anyone do anything?\n\nI dont know, I was really drunk at the time\n\nAfter, I was yelling and screaming and telling him why\n\nIt wasnt coming up on fader eleven\n\nIt came to a heavy blow\n\nWhich sorted the matter out\n\nI dont know, I was really drunk at the time</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMUAT">Us and them\n\nAnd after all\n\nWere only ordinary men\n\nMe and you\n\nGod only knows\n\nIts not what we would choose to do\n\nForward he cried from the rear\n\nAnd the front rank died\n\nThe general sat\n\nAnd the lines on the map\n\nMoved from side to side\n\nBlack and blue\n\nAnd who knows\n\nWhich is which\n\nAnd who is who\n\nUp and down\n\nAnd in the end\n\nIts only round and round, and round\n\nHavent you heard its a battle of words?\n\nThe poster bearer cried\n\nListen son said the man with the gun\n\nTheres room for you inside\n\nI mean, theyre not gonna kill ya\n\nSo like, if you give em a quick short, sharp, shock\n\nThey wont do it again\n\nDig it? I mean he got off lightly\n\nCause I wouldve given him a thrashing\n\nI only hit him once!\n\nIt was only a difference of opinion\n\nBut really, I mean good manners dont cost nothing do they, eh?\n\nDown and out\n\nIt cant be helped\n\nBut theres a lot of it about\n\nWith, without\n\nAnd wholl deny\n\nIts what the fightings all about?\n\nOut of the way\n\nIts a busy day\n\nIve got things on my mind\n\nFor want of the price\n\nOf tea and a slice\n\nThe old man died</string>
    <string name="TDSOTMBD">The lunatic is on the grass\n\nThe lunatic is on the grass\n\nRemembering games and daisy chains and laughs\n\nGot to keep the loonies on the path\n\nThe lunatic is in the hall\n\nThe lunatics are in my hall\n\nThe paper holds their folded faces to the floor\n\nAnd every day the paperboy brings more\n\nAnd if the dam breaks open many years too soon\n\nAnd if there is no room upon the hill\n\nAnd if your head explodes with dark forebodings too\n\nIll see you on the dark side of the moon\n\nThe lunatic is in my head\n\nThe lunatic is in my head\n\nYou raise the blade\n\nYou make the change\n\nYou rearrange me till Im sane\n\nYou lock the door\n\nAnd throw away the key\n\nTheres someone in my head but its not me\n\nAnd if the cloud bursts thunder in your ear\n\nYou shout and no one seems to hear\n\nAnd if the band youre in starts playing different tunes\n\nIll see you on the dark side of the moon\n\nI cant think of anything to say except\n\nI think its marvellous!</string>
    <string name="TDSOTME">All that you touch\n\nAnd all that you see\n\nAll that you taste\n\nAll you feel\n\nAnd all that you love\n\nAnd all that you hate\n\nAll you distrust\n\nAll you save\n\nAnd all that you give\n\nAnd all that you deal\n\nAnd all that you buy, beg, borrow, or steal\n\nAnd all you create\n\nAnd all you destroy\n\nAnd all that you do\n\nAnd all that you say\n\nAnd all that you eat\n\nAnd everyone you meet\n\nAnd all that you slight\n\nAnd everyone you fight\n\nAnd all that is now\n\nAnd all that is gone\n\nAnd all thats to come\n\nAnd everything under the sun is in tune\n\nBut the sun is eclipsed by the moon\n\nThere is no dark side in the moon really\n\nMatter of fact its all dark</string>
    <string name="TDBWDYWFM">As you look around this room tonight\n\nSettle in your seat and dim the lights\n\nDo you want my blood, do you want my tears?\n\nWhat do you want?\n\n(What do you want from me?)\n\nShould I sing until I can’t sing anymore?\n\nPlay these strings until my fingers are raw\n\nYoure so hard to please\n\nWhat do you want from me?\n\nDo you think that I know something you don’t know?\n\n(What do you want from me?)\n\nIf I don’t promise you the answers would you go?\n\n(What do you want from me?)\n\nShould I stand out in the rain?\n\nDo you want me to make a daisy chain for you?\n\nI’m not the one you need\n\nWhat do you want from me?\n\nYou can have anything you want\n\nYou can drift, you can dream, even walk on water\n\nAnything you want\n\nYou can own everything you see\n\nSell your soul for complete control\n\nIs that really what you need?\n\nYou can lose yourself this night\n\nSee inside, there is nothing to hide\n\nTurn and face the light\n\nWhat do you want from me?</string>
    <string name="TDBPA">Did you know\n\nIt was all going to go so wrong for you?\n\nAnd did you see\n\nIt was all going to be so right for me?\n\nWhy did we tell you then\n\nYou were always the golden boy then\n\nAnd that youd never lose that light in your eyes?\n\nHey you\n\nDid you ever realize what youd become?\n\nAnd did you see\n\nThat it wasnt only me you were running from?\n\nDid you know all the time but it\n\nNever bothered you anyway?\n\nLeading the blind while I stared out the steel in your eyes\n\nThe rain fell slow\n\nDown on all the roofs of uncertainty\n\nI thought of you\n\nAnd the years and all the sadness fell away from me\n\nAnd did you know?\n\n(Did you know, did you know, did you know)\n\n(Did you know, did you know, did you know)\n\n(Did you know, did you)\n\nI never thought that youd lose that light in your eye\n\n</string>
    <string name="TDBAGDFF">On the day the wall came down\n\nThey threw the locks onto the ground\n\nAnd with glasses high we raised a cry\n\nFor freedom had arrived\n\nOn the day the wall came down\n\nThe Ship of Fools had finally run aground\n\nPromises lit up the night\n\nLike paper doves in flight\n\nI dreamed you had left my side\n\nNo warmth, not even pride remained\n\nAnd even though you needed me\n\nIt was clear that I could not do a thing for you\n\nNow life devalues day by day\n\nAs friends and neighbors turn away\n\nAnd there’s a change that even with regret\n\nCannot be undone\n\nNow frontiers shift like desert sands\n\nWhile nations wash their bloodied hands\n\nOf loyalty, of history, in shades of grey\n\nI woke to the sound of drums\n\nThe music played, the morning sun streamed in\n\nI turned and I looked at you\n\nAnd all but the bitter residues slipped away\n\nSlipped away</string>
    <string name="TDBWTIO">From morning to night I stayed out of sight\n\nDidn’t recognize I’d become\n\nNo more than alive; I’d barely survive\n\nIn a word, overrun\n\nWon’t hear a sound (He’s curled into the corner)\n\nFrom my mouth (But still the screen is flickering)\n\nI’ve spent too long (With an endless stream of garbage to)\n\nOn the inside out (…curse the place)\n\nMy skin is cold (In a sea of random images)\n\nTo the human touch (The self-destructing animal)\n\nThis bleeding heart’s (Waiting for the waves to break)\n\nNot beating much\n\nI murmured a vow of silence and now\n\nI don’t even hear when I think aloud\n\nExtinguished by light, I turn on the night\n\nWear its darkness with an empty smile\n\nI’m creeping back to life\n\nMy nervous system all awry\n\nI’m wearing the inside out\n\nLook at him now\n\nHe’s paler somehow\n\nBut he’s coming around\n\nHe’s starting to choke\n\nIt’s been so long since he spoke\n\nWell he can have the words right from my mouth\n\nAnd with these words I can see\n\nClear through the clouds that covered me\n\nJust give it time then speak my name\n\nNow we can hear ourselves again\n\nI’m holding out (He’s standing on the threshold)\n\nFor the day (Caught in fiery anger)\n\nWhen all the clouds (And hurled into the furnace he’ll)\n\nHave blown away (…curse the place)\n\nI’m with you now (He’s torn in all directions)\n\nCan speak your name (And still the screen is flickering)\n\nNow we can hear (Waiting for the flames to break)\n\nOurselves again</string>
    <string name="TDBTIB">Her love rains down on me\n\nEasy as the breeze\n\nI listen to her breathing\n\nIt sounds like the waves on the sea\n\nI was thinking all about her\n\nBurning with rage and desire\n\nWe were spinning into darkness\n\nThe earth was on fire\n\nShe could take it back\n\nShe might take it back someday\n\nSo I spy on her, I lie to her\n\nI make promises I cannot keep\n\nThen I hear their laughter rising, rising from the deep\n\nAnd I make her prove her love for me, I take all that I can take\n\nAnd I push her to the limit to see if she will break\n\nShe might take it back, she could take it back some day\n\nRing-a-ring o’ roses\n\nA pocket full of posies\n\nA-tishoo! A-tishoo!\n\nWe all fall down\n\nNow I have seen the warnings, screaming from all sides\n\nIt’s easy to ignore them, God knows I’ve tried\n\nAll of this temptation, you know it turned my faith to lies\n\nUntil I couldn’t see the danger or hear the rising tide\n\nShe can take it back, she will take it back some day\n\nShe can take it back, she will take it back some day\n\nShe will take it back, she will take it back some day</string>
    <string name="TDBCBTL">Where were you when I was burned and broken?\n\nWhile the days slipped by from my window watching\n\nAnd where were you when I was hurt and I was helpless?\n\n‘Cause the things you say and the things you do surround me\n\nWhile you were hanging yourself on someone else’s words\n\nDying to believe in what you heard\n\nI was staring straight into the shining sun\n\nLost in thought and lost in time\n\nWhile the seeds of life and the seeds of change were planted\n\nOutside, the rain fell dark and slow\n\nWhile I pondered on this dangerous but irresistible pastime\n\nI took a heavenly ride through our silence\n\nI knew the moment had arrived\n\nFor killing the past and coming back to life\n\nI took a heavenly ride through our silence\n\nI knew the waiting had begun\n\nAnd headed straight… into the shining sun</string>
    <string name="TDBKT">For millions of years mankind lived just like the animals\n\nThen something happened which unleashed the power of our imagination\n\nWe learned to talk\n\nThere’s a silence surrounding me\n\nI can’t seem to think straight\n\nI’ll sit in the corner\n\nAnd no one can bother me\n\nI think I should speak now (Why won’t you talk to me?)\n\nI can’t seem to speak now (You never talk to me)\n\nMy words won’t come out right (What are you thinking?)\n\nI feel like I’m drowning (What are you feeling?)\n\nI’m feeling weak now (Why won’t you talk to me?)\n\nBut I can’t show my weakness (You never talk to me)\n\nI sometimes wonder (What are you thinking?)\n\nWhere do we go from here (What are you feeling?)\n\nIt doesn’t have to be like this\n\nAll we need to do is make sure we keep talking\n\n(Why won’t you talk to me?) I feel like I’m drowning\n\n(You never talk to me) You know I can’t breathe now\n\n(What are you thinking?) We’re going nowhere\n\n(What are you feeling?) We’re going nowhere\n\n(Why won’t you talk to me?)\n\n(You never talk to me)\n\n(What are you thinking?)\n\n(Where do we go from here?)\n\nIt doesn’t have to be like this\n\nAll we need to do is make sure we keep talking</string>
    <string name="TDBLFW">I was spending my time in the doldrums\n\nI was caught in a cauldron of hate\n\nI felt persecuted and paralysed\n\nI thought that everything else would just wait\n\nWhile you are wasting your time on your enemies\n\nEngulfed in a fever of spite\n\nBeyond your tunnel vision reality fades\n\nLike shadows into the night\n\nTo martyr yourself to caution\n\nIs not gonna help at all\n\n‘Cause there’ll be no safety in numbers\n\nWhen the right one walks out of the door\n\n"Ladies and gentlemen!\n\nThe winner\n\nBy a knockout"\n\nCan you see your days blighted by darkness?\n\nIs it true you beat your fists on the floor?\n\nStuck in a world of isolation\n\nWhile the ivy grows over the door\n\nSo I open my door to my enemies\n\nAnd I ask "Could we wipe the slate clean?"\n\nBut they tell me to please go fuck myself\n\nYou know you just can’t win</string>
    <string name="TDBHH">Beyond the horizon of the place we lived when we were young\n\nIn a world of magnets and miracles\n\nOur thoughts strayed constantly and without boundary\n\nThe ringing of the division bell had begun\n\nAlong the Long Road and on down the Causeway\n\nDo they still meet there by the Cut\n\nThere was a ragged band that followed in our footsteps\n\nRunning before time took our dreams away\n\nLeaving the myriad small creatures trying to tie us to the ground\n\nTo a life consumed by slow decay\n\nThe grass was greener\n\nThe light was brighter\n\nWith friends surrounded\n\nThe nights of wonder\n\nLooking beyond the embers of bridges glowing behind us\n\nTo a glimpse of how green it was on the other side\n\nSteps taken forwards but sleepwalking back again\n\nDragged by the force of some inner tide\n\nAt a higher altitude with flag unfurled\n\nWe reached the dizzy heights of that dreamed of world\n\nEncumbered forever by desire and ambition\n\nTheres a hunger still unsatisfied\n\nOur weary eyes still stray to the horizon\n\nThough down this road weve been so many times\n\nThe grass was greener\n\nThe light was brighter\n\nThe taste was sweeter\n\nThe nights of wonder\n\nWith friends surrounded\n\nThe dawn mist glowing\n\nThe water flowing\n\nThe endless river\n\nFor ever and ever\n\n"Is that Charlie? Hello Charlie!\n\nGreat..."</string>
    <string name="TWITF1">So ya thought ya might like to go to the show\n\nTo feel the warm thrill of confusion, that space cadet glow\n\nTell me, is something eluding you, sunshine?\n\nIs this not what you expected to see?\n\nIf you wanna find out whats behind these cold eyes\n\nYoull just have to claw your way through this disguise\n\nLights!\n\nRoll the sound effects!\n\nAction!\n\nDrop it, drop it on em\n\nDrop it, drop it on them!</string>
    <string name="TWTTI">Momma loves her baby\n\nAnd Daddy loves you too\n\nAnd the sea may look warm to you, babe\n\nAnd the sky may look blue\n\nOoh-ooh-ooh-ooh, babe\n\nOoh-ooh-ooh, baby blue\n\nOoh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, babe\n\nIf you should go skating\n\nOn the thin ice of modern life\n\nDragging behind you, the silent reproach\n\nOf a million tear stained eyes\n\nDont be surprised when a crack in the ice\n\nAppears under your feet\n\nYoull slip out of your depth and out of your mind\n\nWith your fear flowing out behind you\n\nAs you claw the thin ice</string>
    <string name="TWABITW1">Daddys flown across the ocean\n\nLeaving just a memory\n\nA snapshot in the family album\n\nDaddy, what else did you leave for me?\n\nDaddy, whatd ya leave behind for me?\n\nAll in all, it was just a brick in the wall\n\nAll in all, it was all just bricks in the wall</string>
    <string name="TWTHDOOL">You! Yes, you! Stand still, laddie!\n\nWhen we grew up and went to school\n\nThere were certain teachers who\n\nWould hurt the children in any way they could (Oof!)\n\nBy pouring their derision upon anything we did\n\nExposing every weakness\n\nHowever carefully hidden by the kid\n\nBut in the town, it was well known, when they got home at night\n\nTheir fat and psychopathic wives would thrash them within inches of their lives</string>
    <string name="TWABITW2">We dont need no education\n\nWe dont need no thought control\n\nNo dark sarcasm in the classroom\n\nTeacher, leave them kids alone\n\nHey! Teacher! Leave them kids alone!\n\nAll in all, its just another brick in the wall\n\nAll in all, youre just another brick in the wall\n\nWe dont need no education\n\nWe dont need no thought control\n\nNo dark sarcasm in the classroom\n\nTeachers, leave them kids alone\n\nHey! Teacher! Leave us kids alone!\n\nAll in all, youre just another brick in the wall\n\nAll in all, youre just another brick in the wall\n\nWrong, do it again!\n\nWrong, do it again!\n\nIf you dont eat your meat, you cant have any pudding!\n\nHow can you have any pudding if you dont eat your meat?\n\nYou! Yes! You behind the bike sheds! Stand still, laddie!\n\nIf you dont eat your meat, you cant have any pudding!\n\nHow can you have any pudding if you dont eat your meat?\n\nYou! Yes! You behind the bike sheds! Stand still, laddie!</string>
    <string name="TWM">Mother, do you think theyll drop the bomb?\n\nMother, do you think theyll like this song?\n\nMother, do you think theyll try to break my balls?\n\nOoh-ah, Mother, should I build the wall?\n\nMother, should I run for president?\n\nMother, should I trust the government?\n\nMother, will they put me in the firing line?\n\nOoh-ah, is it just a waste of time?\n\nHush now, baby, baby, dont you cry\n\nMammas gonna make all of your nightmares come true\n\nMammas gonna put all of her fears into you\n\nMammas gonna keep you right here, under her wing\n\nShe wont let you fly, but she might let you sing\n\nMammas gonna keep baby cosy and warm\n\nOoh babe, ooh babe, ooh babe\n\nOf course, Mammas gonna help build the wall\n\nMother, do you think shes good enough... For me?\n\nMother, do you think shes dangerous... To me?\n\nMother, will she tear your little boy apart?\n\nOoh-ah, Mother, will she break my heart?\n\nHush now, baby, baby, dont you cry\n\nMammas gonna check out all your girlfriends for you\n\nMamma wont let anyone dirty get through\n\nMammas gonna wait up until you get in\n\nMamma will always find out where youve been\n\nMammas gonna keep baby healthy and clean\n\nOoh babe, ooh babe, ooh babe\n\nYoull always be "baby" to me\n\nMother, did it need to be so high?</string>
    <string name="TWGBS">Look, Mummy!\n\nTheres an airplane up in the sky\n\nOoh-ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh\n\nOoh-ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh\n\nOoh-ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh\n\nDid-did-did-did you see the frightened ones?\n\nDid-did-did-did you hear the falling bombs?\n\nDid-did-did-did you ever wonder why we had to run for shelter when the promise of a brave new world unfurled beneath the clear blue sky?\n\nOoh-ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh\n\nOoh-ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh\n\nDid-did-did-did you see the frightened ones?\n\nDid-did-did-did you hear the falling bombs?\n\nThe flames are all long gone\n\nBut the pain lingers on\n\nGoodbye, blue sky\n\nGoodbye, blue sky\n\nGoodbye\n\nGoodbye</string>
    <string name="TWES">What shall we use to fill the empty spaces\n\nWhere we used to talk?\n\nHow shall I fill the final places?\n\nHow should I complete the wall?</string>
    <string name="TWYL">I am just a new boy\n\nA stranger in this town\n\nWhere are all the good times?\n\nWhos gonna show this stranger around?\n\nOoh, I need a dirty woman\n\nOoh, I need a dirty girl\n\nWill some woman in this desert land\n\nMake me feel like a real man?\n\nTake this rock-and-roll refugee\n\nOoh, baby, set me free\n\nOoh, I need a dirty woman\n\nOoh, I need a dirty girl\n\nOoh, I need a dirty woman\n\nOoh, I need a dirty girl\n\n*Phone beeping*\n\n"Hello?"\n\n"Yes, a collect call for Mrs. Floyd from Mr. Floyd. Will you accept the charge from the United States?"\n\n*Phone clicks*\n\n"Oh, he hung up. Thats your residence, right? Well, I wonder why he hung up. Is there supposed to be someone out there besides your wife there to answer?"\n\n*Phone redials and beeps again*\n\n"Hello?"\n\n"This is the United States calling. Are we reaching..."\n\n*Phone clicks*\n\n"See, he keeps hanging up, and its a man answering."</string>
    <string name="TWOOMT">"Oh my God! What a fabulous room! Are all these your guitars?"\n\n"God! This place is bigger than our apartment!"\n\n"Um, can I get a drink of water?"\n\n"You want some, huh?"\n\n"Oh wow! Hey, look at this tub! Wanna take a bath?"\n\n"What are you watching?"\n\n"Hello?"\n\n"Are you feeling okay?"\n\nDay after day, the love turns gray\n\nLike the skin of the dying man\n\nAnd night after night, we pretend its all right\n\nBut I have grown older, and you have grown colder\n\nAnd nothing is very much fun any more\n\nAnd I can feel one of my turns coming on\n\nI feel cold as a razor blade, tight as a tourniquet\n\nDry as a funeral drum\n\nRun to the bedroom, in the suitcase on the left\n\nYoull find my favourite axe\n\nDont look so frightened, this is just a passing phase\n\nOne of my bad days\n\nWould you like to watch TV? Or get between the sheets?\n\nOr contemplate the silent freeway?\n\nWould you like something to eat? Would you like to learn to fly?\n\nWould ya? Would you like to see me try?\n\nAh, no!\n\nWould you like to call the cops?\n\nDo you think its time I stopped?\n\nWhy are you running away?</string>
    <string name="TWDLMN">Ooh, babe, dont leave me now\n\nDont say its the end of the road\n\nRemember the flowers I sent\n\nI need you, babe\n\nTo put through the shredder in front of my friends\n\nOh, babe, dont leave me now\n\nHow could you go?\n\nWhen you know how I need you\n\nTo beat to a pulp on a Saturday night\n\nOh, babe, dont leave me now\n\nHow can you treat me this way?\n\nRunning away\n\nOoh, babe, why are you running away?\n\nOoh, babe\n\nOoh, babe\n\nOoh, babe</string>
    <string name="TWABITW3">I dont need no arms around me\n\nAnd I dont need no drugs to calm me\n\nI have seen the writing on the wall\n\nDont think I need anything at all\n\nNo, dont think Ill need anything at all\n\nAll in all, it was all just bricks in the wall\n\nAll in all, you were all just bricks in the wall</string>
    <string name="TWGCW">Goodbye, cruel world, Im leaving you today\n\nGoodbye, goodbye, goodbye\n\nGoodbye, all you people, theres nothing you can say\n\nTo make me change my mind, goodbye</string>
    <string name="TWHY">Hey you\n\nOut there in the cold, getting lonely, getting old\n\nCan you feel me?\n\nHey you\n\nStanding in the aisles with itchy feet and fading smiles\n\nCan you feel me?\n\nHey you\n\nDont help them to bury the light\n\nDont give in without a fight\n\nHey you\n\nOut there on your own, sitting naked by the phone\n\nWould you touch me?\n\nHey you\n\nWith your ear against the wall, waiting for someone to call out\n\nCould you touch me?\n\nHey you\n\nWould you help me to carry the stone?\n\nOpen your heart, Im coming home\n\nBut it was only fantasy\n\nThe wall was too high, as you can see\n\nNo matter how he tried, he could not break free\n\nAnd the worms ate into his brain\n\nHey you\n\nOut there on the road, always doing what youre told\n\nCan you help me?\n\nHey you\n\nOut there beyond the wall, breaking bottles in the hall\n\nCan you help me?\n\nHey you\n\nDont tell me theres no hope at all\n\nTogether we stand, divided we fall</string>
    <string name="TWITAOT">"Well, only got an hour of daylight left. Better get started"\n\n"Isnt it unsafe to travel at night?"\n\n"Itll be a lot less safe to stay here. Your fathers gonna pick up our trail before long"\n\n"Can Lorca ride?"\n\n"Hell have to ride. Lorca, time to go! Chengra, thank you for everything. Lets go."\n\n"Goodbye, Chengra"\n\n"Goodbye, Missy!"\n\n"Ill be back--one day"\n\nIs there anybody out there?\n\nIs there anybody out there?\n\nIs there anybody out there?\n\nAh, is there anybody out there?</string>
    <string name="TWNH">"But theres somebody else that needs taking care of in Washington..."\n\n"Whos that?"\n\n"Rose Pilchitt!"\n\n"Rose Pilchitt? Whos that?"\n\n*Kid screams in background*\n\n"36-24-36 *Laughs* does that answer your question?"\n\n(Oi! Ive got a little black book with me poems in!)\n\n"Whos she?"\n\n"She was Miss Armoured Division in 1961... "\n\nIve got a little black book with my poems in\n\nGot a bag with a toothbrush and a comb in\n\nWhen Im a good dog they sometimes throw me a bone in\n\nI got elastic bands keeping my shoes on\n\nGot those swollen hand blues\n\nIve got thirteen channels of shit on the T.V. to choose from\n\nIve got electric light\n\nAnd Ive got second sight\n\nIve got amazing powers of observation\n\nAnd that is how I know\n\nWhen I try to get through\n\nOn the telephone to you\n\nThere will be nobody home\n\nIve got the obligatory Hendrix perm\n\nAnd the inevitable pinhole burns\n\nAll down the front of my favourite satin shirt\n\nIve got nicotine stains on my fingers\n\nIve got a silver spoon on a chain\n\nIve got a grand piano to prop up my mortal remains\n\nIve got wild staring eyes\n\nAnd Ive got a strong urge to fly\n\nBut Ive got nowhere to fly to (Fly to... fly to... fly to...)\n\nOoh, babe, when I pick up the phone\n\n("Surprise, surprise, surprise...")\n\nTheres still nobody home\n\nIve got a pair of Gohills boots\n\nAnd Ive got fading roots</string>
    <string name="TWV">Does anybody here remember Vera Lynn?\n\nRemember how she said that\n\nWe would meet again some sunny day?\n\nVera, Vera, what has become of you?\n\nDoes anybody else in here feel the way I do?</string>
    <string name="TWBTBBH">Bring the boys back home\n\nBring the boys back home\n\nDont leave the children on their own, no, no\n\nBring the boys back home\n\n"Wrong, do it again!"\n\n*Knock* "Time to go!"\n\n"Are you feeling okay?"\n\n"He keeps hanging up, and its a man answering!"\n\n"Hahahahaha!!!!!!"\n\nIs there anybody out there?</string>
    <string name="TWCN">Hello?\n\nIs there anybody in there?\n\nJust nod if you can hear me\n\nIs there anyone home?\n\nCome on (Come on, come on), now\n\nI hear youre feeling down\n\nWell, I can ease your pain\n\nAnd get you on your feet again\n\nRelax (Relax, relax, relax)\n\nIll need some information first\n\nJust the basic facts\n\nCan you show me where it hurts?\n\nThere is no pain, you are receding\n\nA distant ship, smoke on the horizon\n\nYou are only coming through in waves\n\nYour lips move, but I cant hear what youre saying\n\nWhen I was a child, I had a fever\n\nMy hands felt just like two balloons\n\nNow Ive got that feeling once again\n\nI cant explain, you would not understand\n\nThis is not how I am\n\nI have become comfortably numb\n\nI have become comfortably numb\n\nOkay (Okay, okay, okay)\n\nJust a little pinprick\n\nTherell be no more\n\nBut you may feel a little sick\n\nCan you stand up? (Stand up, stand up)\n\nI do believe its working, good\n\nThatll keep you going through the show\n\nCome on, its time to go\n\nThere is no pain, you are receding\n\nA distant ship, smoke on the horizon\n\nYou are only coming through in waves\n\nYour lips move, but I cant hear what youre saying\n\nWhen I was a child, I caught a fleeting glimpse\n\nOut of the corner of my eye\n\nI turned to look, but it was gone\n\nI cannot put my finger on it now\n\nThe child is grown, the dream is gone\n\nI have become comfortably numb</string>
    <string name="TWTSMGO">Must the show go on?\n\nTake me home, take me home, take me home\n\nLet me go, let me go, let me go\n\nThere must be some mistake, I didnt mean to let them\n\nTake away my soul, am I too old, is it too late?\n\nWhere has the feeling gone?\n\nWill I remember the song?\n\nThe show must go on</string>
    <string name="TWITF2">So ya thought ya might like to go to the show\n\nTo feel the warm thrill of confusion, that space cadet glow\n\nIve got some bad news for you sunshine\n\nPink isnt well, he stayed back at the hotel\n\nAnd they sent us along as a surrogate band\n\nWere gonna find out where you fans really stand\n\nAre there any queers in the theater tonight?\n\nGet them up against the wall\n\n(Against the wall)\n\nNow theres one in the spotlight, he dont look right to me\n\nGet him up against the wall\n\n(Against the—)\n\nAnd that one looks Jewish and that ones a coon!\n\nWho let all of this riff-raff into the room?\n\nTheres one smoking a joint and another with spots\n\nIf I had my way, Id have all of them shot!</string>
    <string name="TWRLH">Run, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nYou better make your face up with your favourite disguise\n\nWith your button down lips and your roller blind eyes\n\nWith your empty smile and your hungry heart\n\nFeel the bile rising from your guilty past\n\nWith your nerves in tatters as the cockleshell shatters\n\nAnd the hammers batter down your door\n\nYou better run!\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nRun, run, run, run\n\nYou better run all day and run all night\n\nAnd keep your dirty feelings deep inside\n\nAnd if youre taking your girlfriend out tonight\n\nYou better park the car well out of sight\n\nCause if they catch you in the back seat trying to pick her locks\n\nTheyre gonna send you back to Mother in a cardboard box\n\nYou better run!</string>
    <string name="TWWFTW">Ooh-ooh, you cannot reach me now\n\nOoh-ooh, no matter how you try\n\nGoodbye, cruel world, its over\n\nWalk on by\n\nSitting in a bunker here behind my wall\n\nWaiting for the worms to come (Worms to come)\n\nIn perfect isolation here behind my wall\n\nWaiting for the worms to come\n\nTesting. One. Two. One. Two. We’re all going to convene at 1:15 outside Brixton Town Hall where we will be going...\n\nWaiting\n\nTo cut out the deadwood\n\nWaiting\n\nTo clean up the city\n\nWaiting\n\nTo follow the worms\n\nWaiting\n\nTo put on a black shirt\n\nWaiting\n\nTo weed out the weaklings\n\nWaiting\n\nTo smash in their windows and kick in their doors\n\nWaiting\n\nFor the final solution to strengthen the strain\n\nWaiting\n\nTo follow the worms\n\nWaiting\n\nTo turn on the showers and fire the ovens\n\nWaiting\n\nFor the queers and the coons and the reds and the Jews\n\nWaiting\n\nTo follow the worms\n\nWould you like to see Britannia Rule again\n\nMy friend?\n\nAll you have to do is follow the worms\n\nWould you like to send our coloured cousins home again\n\nMy friend?\n\nAll you need to do is follow the worms</string>
    <string name="TWS">I wanna go home\n\nTake off this uniform and leave the show\n\nBut Im waiting in this cell, because I have to know\n\nHave I been guilty all this time?</string>
    <string name="TWTT">Good morning, Worm your honour\n\nThe crown will plainly show the prisoner\n\nWho now stands before you\n\nWas caught red-handed showing feelings\n\nShowing feelings of an almost human nature\n\nThis will not do\n\nCall the schoolmaster!\n\nI always said hed come to no good in the end your honour\n\nIf theyd let me have my way I could have flayed him into shape\n\nBut my hands were tied, the bleeding hearts and artists\n\nLet him get away with murder, let me hammer him today\n\nCrazy, toys in the attic\n\nI am crazy, truly gone fishing\n\nThey must have taken my marbles away!\n\nCrazy, toys in the attic, he is crazy\n\nYou little shit, youre in it now, I hope they throw away the key\n\nYou should have talked to me more often than you did, but no!\n\nYou had to go your own way\n\nHave you broken any homes up lately?\n\n"Just five minutes, Worm your honour, him and me, alone"\n\nBabe!\n\nCome to mother baby, let me hold you in my arms\n\nMlud I never wanted him to get in any trouble\n\nWhyd he ever have to leave me?\n\nWorm, your honour, let me take him home\n\nCrazy, over the rainbow\n\nI am crazy, bars in the window\n\nThere must have been a door there in the wall\n\nWhen I came in\n\nCrazy, over the rainbow, he is crazy\n\nThe evidence before the court is incontrovertible\n\nTheres no need for the jury to retire\n\nIn all my years of judging, I have never heard before\n\nOf someone more deserving of the full penalty of law\n\nThe way you made them suffer, your exquisite wife and mother\n\nFills me with the urge to defecate\n\nGo on, Judge, shit on him!\n\nSince, my friend, you have revealed your deepest fear\n\nI sentence you to be exposed before your peers\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!\n\nTear down the wall!</string>
    <string name="TWOTW">All alone, or in twos\n\nThe ones who really love you\n\nWalk up and down, outside the wall\n\nSome hand in hand\n\nAnd some gathered together in bands\n\nThe bleeding hearts and the artists make their stand\n\nAnd when theyve given you their all\n\nSome stagger and fall, after all its not easy\n\nBanging your heart against some mad buggers wall\n\nIsnt this where...</string>
    <string name="AHMI">If I were a swan, Id be gone\n\nIf I were a swan, Id be gone\n\nIf I were a train, Id be late\n\nAnd if I were a good man\n\nId talk with you more often than I do\n\nIf I were asleep, I could dream\n\nIf I were afraid, I could hide\n\nIf I go insane\n\nPlease dont put your wires in my brain\n\nIf I were the moon, Id be cool\n\nIf I were a rule, I would bend\n\nIf I were a good man\n\nId understand the spaces between friends\n\nIf I were alone, I would cry\n\nAnd if I were with you, Id be home and dry\n\nAnd if I go insane\n\nWill you still let me join in with the game?\n\nIf I were a swan, Id be gone\n\nIf I were a train, Id be late again\n\nIf I were a good man\n\nId talk with you more often than I do</string>
    <string name="AHMS">Would you like to say\n\nPerhaps youd care to state exactly how you feel\n\nWe say goodbye before weve said hello\n\nI hardly even like you, I shouldnt care at all\n\nWe met just six hours ago, the music was too loud\n\nFrom your bed I gained a day and lost a bloody year\n\nAnd I would like to know\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nNot a single word was said, the night still hid our fears\n\nOccasionally you showed a smile but what was the need\n\nI felt the cold far too soon in a room of 95\n\nMy friends are lying in the sun, I wish that I was there\n\nTomorrow brings another town another girl like you\n\nHave you time before you leave to greet another man?\n\nJust you let me know\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nHow do you feel?\n\nGoodbye to you, Charlotte Pringles due\n\nIve had enough for one day</string>
    <string name="AHMFOS">When that fat old sun in the sky is falling\n\nSummer evening birds are calling\n\nSummer Sunday and a year\n\nThe sound of music in my ears\n\nDistant bells, new mown grass smells so sweet\n\nBy the river holding hands\n\nRoll me up and lay me down\n\nAnd if you see, don’t make a sound\n\nPick your feet up off the ground\n\nAnd if you hear as the warm night falls\n\nThe silver sound from a tongue so strange\n\nSing to me, sing to me\n\nWhen that fat old sun in the sky is falling\n\nSummer evening birds are calling\n\nChildren’s laughter in my ears\n\nThe last sunlight disappears\n\nAnd if you see, don’t make a sound\n\nPick your feet up off the ground\n\nAnd if you hear as the warm night falls\n\nThe silver sound from a tongue so strange\n\nSing to me, sing to me\n\nWhen that fat old sun in the sky is falling</string>
    <string name="AHMAPB">Oh, uh, me flakes, then uh, scrambled eggs, bacon, sausages, tomatoes\n\nToast, coffee\n\nMarmalade, I like marmalade. Yes, porridge is nice. Any cereal, I like all cereals\n\nOh God. Kickoff is 10am\n\nBreakfast in Los Angeles, macrobiotic stuff\n\nI dont mind a barrow, I like barrowing the stuff in\n\nIve got a terrible back. When I work, it hurts me\n\nDyou know what I mean, John?\n\nWell hes sort of, err… when driving on the road, he gets ready for the gig, he has a sleep\n\nI dont know\n\nHe does all the electrical stuff. I cant be bothered with that its so fiddly\n\nAll my heads a blank</string>
    <string name="MeOOTD">One of these days, I’m going to cut you into little pieces</string>
    <string name="MeAPOW">A cloud of eiderdown\n\nDraws around me\n\nSoftening the sound\n\nSleepy time, when I lie\n\nWith my love by my side\n\nAnd she’s breathing low\n\nAnd the candle dies\n\nWhen night comes down, you lock the door\n\nThe book falls to the floor\n\nAs darkness falls and waves roll by\n\nThe seasons change, the wind is warm\n\nNow wakes the owl, now sleeps the swan\n\nBehold a dream, the dream is gone\n\nGreen fields, a cold rain is falling\n\nIn a golden dawn\n\nAnd deep beneath the ground\n\nThe early morning sounds\n\nAnd I go down\n\nSleepy time, when I lie\n\nWith my love by my side\n\nAnd she’s breathing low\n\nAnd I rise, like a bird\n\nIn the haze, when the first rays\n\nTouch the sky\n\nAnd the night winds die</string>
    <string name="MeF">You say the hills too steep to climb\n\nChiding\n\nYou say you’d like to see me try\n\nClimbing\n\nYou pick the place and I’ll choose the time\n\nAnd I will climb that hill in my own way\n\nJust wait a while for the right day\n\nAnd as I rise above the tree line and the clouds\n\nI look down, hearing the sound of the things you’ve said today\n\nFearlessly the idiot faced the crowd\n\nSmiling\n\nMerciless the magistrate turns ’round\n\nFrowning\n\nAnd who’s the fool who wears the crown?\n\nAnd go down in your own way\n\nAnd every day is the right day\n\nAnd as you rise above the fear-lines in his brow\n\nYou look down, hearing the sound of the faces in the crowd\n\nWalk on, walk on, with hope in your heart\n\nAnd youll never walk alone\n\nYoull never walk alone\n\nLiverpool! Liverpool!</string>
    <string name="MeST">As I reach for a peach, slide a rind down behind\n\nThe sofa in San Tropez\n\nBreakin’ a stick with a brick on the sand\n\nRidin’ a wave in the wake of an old sedan\n\nSleepin’ alone in the drone of the darkness\n\nScratched by the sand that fell from my love\n\nDeep in my dreams and I still hear her callin’\n\n“If you’re alone, I’ll come ho-ho-home”\n\nBackward and homebound, the pigeon, the dove\n\nGone with the wind and the rain, on an airplane\n\nBorn in a home with no silver spoon\n\nI’m drinking champagne like a good tycoon\n\nSooner than wait for a break in the weather\n\nI’ll gather my far-flung thoughts together\n\nSpeeding away on the wind to a new day\n\nIf you’re alone, I’ll come ho-ho-home\n\nAnd I pause for a while by a country stile\n\nAnd listen to the things they say\n\nDiggin’ for gold in a hole in my hand\n\nOpen a book, take a look at the way things stand\n\nAnd you’re leading me down to the place by the sea\n\nI hear your soft voice calling to me\n\nMaking a date for later by phone\n\nAnd if you’re alone, I’ll come ho-ho-home</string>
    <string name="MeS">I was in the kitchen\n\nSeamus, that’s the dog, was outside\n\nWell, I was in the kitchen\n\nSeamus, my old hound, was outside\n\nWell you know, the sun sinks slowly\n\nBut my old hound dog sat right down and cried</string>
    <string name="MeE">Overhead the albatross\n\nHangs motionless upon the air\n\nAnd deep beneath the rolling waves in labyrinths of coral caves\n\nThe echo of a distant time comes willowing across the sand\n\nAnd everything is green and submarine\n\nAnd no one showed us to the land\n\nAnd no one knows the wheres or whys\n\nBut something stirs and something tries\n\nAnd starts to climb towards the light\n\nStrangers passing in the street\n\nBy chance two separate glances meet\n\nAnd I am you\n\nAnd what I see is me\n\nAnd do I take you by the hand\n\nAnd lead you through the land\n\nAnd help me understand the best I can?\n\nAnd no one calls us to move on\n\nAnd no one forces down our eyes\n\nNo one speaks and no one tries\n\nNo one flies around the sun\n\nCloudless every day you fall\n\nUpon my waking eyes\n\nInviting and inciting me to rise\n\nAnd through the window in the wall\n\nCome streaming in on sunlight wings\n\nA million bright ambassadors of morning\n\nAnd no one sings me lullabies\n\nAnd no one makes me close my eyes\n\nSo I throw the windows wide\n\nAnd call to you across the sky</string>
    <string name="TERTLU">We certainly have an unspoken understanding\n\nBut a lot of things unsaid as well\n\nWe shout and argue and fight, and work it on out\n\nThe sum is greater than the parts</string>
    <string name="TERTH">Speech has allowed the communication of ideas, enabling human beings to work together to build the impossible\n\nMankinds greatest achievements have come about by talking\n\nOur greatest hopes could become reality in the future, with the technology at our disposal, the possibilities are unbounded\n\nAll we need to do is make sure we keep talking</string>
    <string name="TERLTW">We bitch and we fight\n\nDiss each other on sight\n\nBut this thing we do\n\nThese times together\n\nRain or shine or stormy weather\n\nThis thing we do\n\nWith world-weary grace\n\nWeve taken our places\n\nWe could curse it or nurse it and give it a name\n\nOr stay home by the fire, felled by desire\n\nStoking the flame\n\nBut we’re here for the ride\n\nIts louder than words\n\nThis thing that we do\n\nLouder than words\n\nThe way it unfurls\n\nIts louder than words\n\nThe sum of our parts\n\nThe beat of our hearts\n\nIs louder than words\n\nLouder than words\n\nThe strings bend and slide\n\nAs the hours glide by\n\nAn old pair of shoes, your favorite blues\n\nGonna tap out the rhythm\n\nLets go with the flow, wherever it goes\n\nWere more than alive\n\nIts louder than words\n\nThis thing that we do\n\nLouder than words\n\nThe way it unfurls\n\nIts louder than words\n\nThe sum of our parts\n\nThe beat of our hearts\n\nIs louder than words\n\nLouder than words\n\nLouder than words\n\nThis thing they call soul\n\nIs there with a pulse\n\nLouder than words\n\nLouder than words</string>
</resources>